Guide to the University of Chicago Department of History Records 1905-1990
University of Chicago Library
University of Chicago. Department of History. Records
1905-1990
29 linear feet (58 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
This collection contains records from the Department of History at the University of Chicago. The collections contains correspondence, memoranda, minutes, letters of recommendation, examinations, reports, proposals, student lists and student evaluations.
Information on Use
Access
This collection is open for research with the exception of Series IV, which will not be fully available until 2064.
Scope Note
The Department of History Records contain correspondence, memoranda, minutes, letters of recommendation, examinations, reports, proposals, student lists and student evaluations.
The collection is organized into four series:
Series I contains correspondence between faculty, administrators, students, and librarians. The series also contains letters of inquiry and applications sent to the department of history. Series I is divided into six subseries.
Series II contains departmental minutes and other executive papers, administrative memos, reports and proposals, applications to faculty positions, Fishbein Center papers, and library administration papers. Series II is divided into eight subseries.
Series III contains unrestricted student records for M.A., Ph.D., and other students, records of fellowships and scholarships, student recommendation letters, copies of course examinations, course schedules, course reading lists, memos of work, and papers pertaining to student organizations and clubs. Series III is divided into six subseries.
Series IV contains material that is restricted for R-P30, R-50, and R-80 years. The collection contains restricted administrative and student papers, including material from the council of the university senate, financial and personnel material, departmental minutes, evaluated student work and recommendations, fellowship data, and instructors’ reports. Series IV is divided into two subseries and the entire series will be available in 2064.
Related Resources
Browse finding aids by topic.
Subject Headings
University of Chicago. Dept. of History -- History;; University of Chicago -- History
INVENTORY
- Series I: Correspondence
  Series I contains correspondence between faculty, administrators, students, and librarians. The series also contains letters of inquiry and applications sent to the department of history. Series I is divided into six subseries.
  Subseries 1 contains intra-faculty correspondence; subseries 2 contains correspondence pertaining to personnel; subseries 3 contains general faculty correspondence; subseries 4 contains student correspondence; subseries 5 contains library correspondence; and subseries 6 contains letters of inquiry and applications.
  - Subseries 1: Intra-Faculty Correspondence
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 1, 1910-1914 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 2, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 3, 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 4, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 5, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 6, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 7, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 8, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 9, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 10, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 11, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 12, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 13, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 14, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 15, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 16, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 17, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 18, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 19, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 20, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 21, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 22, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 23, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 24, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 25, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 26, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 27, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 28, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 29, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 30, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 31, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 32, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 33, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 34, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 35, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 36, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Intra-Faculty Correspondence, Folder 37, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2: Personnel Correspondence
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 1, 1910-1918 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 2, 1919-1922 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 3, 1923-1924 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 4, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 5, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 6, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 7, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 8, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 9, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 10, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 11, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 12, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 13, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Folder 14, 1938-1948 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Faculty Gray Sheets, Folder 15, 1929-1942 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Correspondence, Faculty Gray Sheets, Folder 16, 1943-1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1924-1939 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Student Appointments, 1922-1934 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: General Faculty Correspondence
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 1, 1910-1916 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 2, 1917-1920 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 3, 1921-1922 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 4, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 5, 1924-1925 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 6, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 7, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 8, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 9, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 10, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 11, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 12, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 13, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 14, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 15, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 16, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 17, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 18, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 19, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 20, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 21, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 22, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 23, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 24, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 25, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 26, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 27, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 28, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 29, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 30, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Correspondence, Folder 31, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 4: Student Correspondence
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 1, 1910-1915 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 2, 1910-1920 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 3, 1921-1923 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 4, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 5, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 6, 1924-1925 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 7, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 8, 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 9, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 10, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 11, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 12, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 13, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 14, 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 15, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 16, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 17, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Student Correspondence, Folder 18, 1942-1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 5: Library Correspondence
    - History, Library Correspondence, Folder 1, 1910-1923 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - History, Library Correspondence, Folder 2, 1924-1926 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - History, Library Correspondence, Folder 3, 1927-1930 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - History, Library Correspondence, Folder 4, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - History, Library Correspondence, Folder 5, 1933-1948 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - History, Library Correspondence, Report for Library Survey, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Library, Kaspi, Andre, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 6: Inquiries and Applications
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 1, 1910-1915 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 2, 1916-1920 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 3, 1921-1922 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 4, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 5, 1924-1925 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 6, 1926-1928 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 7, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 8, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 9, 1932-1934 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 10, 1935-1937 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 11, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 12, 1940-1943 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Inquiries and Applications, Folder 13, 1944-1948 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Letters of Inquiry, History, Folder 1, 1913-1926 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Letters of Inquiry, History, Folder 2, 1927-1931 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Letters of Inquiry, History, Folder 3, 1932-1936 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Letters of Inquiry, History, Folder 4. 1937-1940 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Letters of Inquiry, History, Folder 5, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Letters of Inquiry, History, Folder 6, 1942-1948 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Series II: Administrative Materials
  Series II contains departmental minutes and other executive papers, administrative memos, reports and proposals, applications to faculty positions, Fishbein Center papers, and library administration papers. Series II is divided into eight subseries.
  Subseries 1 contains departmental minutes; subseries 2 contains executive papers; subseries 3 contains administrative memos and notices; subseries 4 contains reports and proposals; subseries 5 contains applications for faculty positions; subseries 6 contains Fishbein Center materials; subseries 7 contains library administration papers; and subseries 8 contains miscellaneous administrative materials.
  - Subseries 1: Departmental Minutes
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Folder 1, 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Folder 2, 1918-1923 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Folder 3, 1924-1927 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Original, Folder 4, 1928-1931 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Copy, Folder 5, 1928-1931 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Original, Folder 6, 1932-1941 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Copy, Folder 7, 1932-1941 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Original, Folder 8, 1942-1946 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - History, Departmental Minutes, Copy, Folder 9, 1942-1946 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Executive Papers
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 1, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 2, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 3, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 4, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 5, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 6, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 7, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 8, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 9, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 10, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 11, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 12, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 13, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 14, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 15, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 16, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 1, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 2, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 3, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 4, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 5, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 6, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 7, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - History, Executive Committee, Divisional Meetings, Folder 8, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - History, Faculty Appointments, Recommendation Forms, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - History, Field Committee, Students Meeting, Memos, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - History, Faculty Losses and Gains, Folder 1, 1968-1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - History, Faculty Losses and Gains, Folder 2, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - History, Faculty Losses and Gains, Folder 3, 1970-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - History, Field Committees, Folder 1, 1969-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - History, Field Committees, Folder 2, 1970-1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - History, Faculty Research, Reports, Folder 1, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - History, Faculty Research, Reports, Folder 2, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - History, Promotional Cases, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - History, Internships, Misc. Papers, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - History, University of Chicago, Fact Book, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - History, Fields of Graduate Study, Brochures, 1978-1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - History, Committee Report, C.M. Gray, Interim, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - History, Committee on Recruitment, Papers, Folder 1, 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - History, Committee on Recruitment, Papers, Folder 2, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - History, Committee on Recruitment, Papers, Folder 3, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - History, Undergraduate History Council, Folder 1, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - History, Undergraduate History Council, Folder 2, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 1, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 2, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 3, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - History, Executive Committee, Papers, Folder 4, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 7, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - History, Office of Sponsored Programs, Memos, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - History, South Asian Field Committee, Papers, 1977-1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - History, Grade Distribution Charts, 1911-1913 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - History, Grade Distribution Charts, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - History, Graduate Students, Lists, 1928-1939 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - History, Nature of History, Lectures, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - History, Fiftieth Anniversary, Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - History, Department Newsletter, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - History, Annual Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - History, American Search, 1970-1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - History, Anglo-American Conference of Historians, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - History, American Field Committee, Folder 1, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - History, American Field Committee, Folder 2, 1974-1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - History, Dean’s Office, Work Reports, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - History, William E. Dodd, Fight for the Northwest, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 1, 1970-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 2, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 3, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 4, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 5, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 6, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - History, Big Ten, Meeting, Folder 7, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - History, Dean of Students, Realignment, 1971-1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - History, Internal Audit, Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - History, Archivist Materials, Folder 1, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - History, Archivist Materials, Folder 2, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - History, Archivist Correspondence and Meeting Arrangements, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - History, Bradburn, Committee Report, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - History, Buckley Amendment, Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - History, Social Sciences, Divisional Meetings, 1974-1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - History, AHA, Papers, Folder 1, 1968-1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - History, AHA, Papers, Folder 2, 1972-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - History, AHA, Programs and Annual Reports, Folder 1, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - History, AHA, Programs and Annual Reports, Folder 2, 1976-1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - History, AHA, Dallas, Folder 1, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - History, AHA, Dallas, Folder 2, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - History, AHA, San Francisco, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - History, AHA, New York, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - History, Processing, Statistics, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3: Administrative Notices
    - History Department, Administrative Notices, Folder 1, 1923-1924 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - History Department, Administrative Notices, Folder 2, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - History Department, Administrative Notices, Folder 3, 1926-1928 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - History Department, Miscellaneous Notices, Folder 1, 1928-1933 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - History Department, Miscellaneous Notices, Folder 2, 1934-1939 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - History Department, Department Notices, Folder 1, 1928-1937 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - History Department, Department Notices, Folder 2, 1938-1948 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - History Department, Notices, University Regulations and Notices, 1939-1947 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - History, Statistical History of the Department, Morrison, 1968-1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - History, Directory of MA/PhD Theses, Urban Studies, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - History, Time Schedules, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - History, Latin America, Grant, Folder 1, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - History, Latin America, Grant, Folder 2, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - History, Turkish Government Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - History, National Assessment of PhD Program, Statistics, Rothblatt, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - History, Summer Teaching, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4: Reports and Proposals
    - History, Social Sciences, Publications, Proposal, Folder 1, 1922-1927 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - History, Social Sciences, Publications, Proposal, Folder 2, 1922-1927 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - History, Albion W. Small, Report, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - History, Social Science Group, Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - History, Honors Courses, Report, 1929-1942 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - History, Curriculum Committee, Report, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - History, Registrar, Reports, Folder 1, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - History, Registrar, Reports, Folder 2, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - History, Registrar, Reports, Folder 3, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - History, Registrar, Reports, Folder 4, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - History, Registrar, Reports, Folder 5, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - History, Reassessment of Appointments Committee, Papers, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Social Science Division, Publications, Reports, 1976-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - History, Record, Evaluation of Department, Folder 1, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - History, Record, Evaluation of Department, Folder 2, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - History, Resident Head, Memos, 1977-1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - History, Department Report, Folder 1, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - History, Department Report, Folder 2, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - History, Morrison, State of the Department, Folder 1, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - History, Morrison, State of the Department, Folder 2, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - History, University Mailings, 1965-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - History, Undergraduate Teaching Survey, Folder 1, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - History, Undergraduate Teaching Survey, Folder 2, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 1, 1974-1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 2, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - History, Triennial Report, Folder 1, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)